1. Download Visual Studio if not already done
2. Download Macaron (the unpacker) and extract the .zip -> https://github.com/Azukee/Macaron
3. Open ArchiveUnpacker.sln in Visual Studio
4.  Right Click on ArchiveUnpacker.CommandLine and build it.
5. Go to where you extracted Macaron and go to ..\ArchiveUnpacker.CommandLine\bin\Debug\net472
6. Right-click on Macaron.exe and click on create shortcut
7. Right-click on the shortcut and go to properties
8. In the "Target" filed, ADD (not replace) after the quotation mark "-extract pathToTroubleDays"
9. Apply it and run the shortcut
10. Copy the content from the new "Extracted" folder and paste it in your TroubleDays directory.
11. Delete all the .pfs in your TroubleDays directory to make sure it uses the scripts and images in the folders
12. You're done! You can now mod the game!

In this repo, there is a file that can help you make your own script named ast_syntax. To call this new script, go in script/gamestart.ast and replace all the "00_1章_共通1" with your script's name.